一蹶不振
當我失去所有希望
I felt so broken
when I lost my faith one day
碎成一片，
好似被推翻的花盆
like a pot knocked over,
made out of clay
如此痛苦，我鎖上心扉
And it hurt so bad,
my chest locked up
我至此仍未定驚魂
The pain made me
go into shock
感覺像失去所愛一樣
有如羽毛般脆弱，一擊不堪
It felt like losing someone I love,
the fragile feathers taken from this dove
噢，但我知道我得向前邁進
Ooh, but I knew I must carry on
疤痕會隨著時間漸漸淡去
The pain will fade as I move along
只要我的心保持堅強
in the hearts that are loyally strong
希望總會迎風而上
Faith will always flutter on
不是對天子皇帝
的盲目服從
Not by the blind submission
to rulers and kings,
而是如比翼鳥般
的心靈融合
but the bond we share,
like two birds of a wing
我們得學會如何飛翔
飛過這些年無心所造成的傷
We must learn to hover on
from all the careless damage that we've done
向前邁進
Carry On
活著才能夠繼續歌唱
Live to sing another song
升起的朝陽
是為了所有人而繼續發光
The rising sun
is shining bright for everyone
向前邁進
Carry On
活出生命的色彩
Live prosperous and long
誰都想知道
未來會帶你到哪去
One tends to wonder
what the future has in store
只因回憶過往不是辦法
when the past won't give out joy anymore
我的笑容還是那麼虛偽
And I just keep faking every smile
我又在原地來回轉圈
I walk another pointless mile
我的悲傷何時才會結束
I don't know when my sorrow will cease
我已厭倦這條熟悉的迴路
for all I know it's just another piece
Ooh, but I know I must carry on
噢, 但我知道我得向前邁進
疤痕會隨著時間漸漸淡去
The pain will fade as I move along
只要我的心保持堅強
in the hearts that are loyally strong
希望總會...
Faith will always...
向前邁進
Carry On
活著才能夠繼續歌唱
Live to sing another song
升起的朝陽
是為了所有人而繼續發光
The rising sun
is shining bright for everyone
向前邁進
Carry on
從今天起定好目標
Be the change you want to see
只有你能做到
You're only one
只要你肯相信自己
It all comes down to what you believe
向前邁進
Carry On
你要勇敢
並向前邁進
Be valiant
and Carry On
活出生命的色彩
Live prosperous and long